ALES Labor Plays 5225 L
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ALES Labor Plays
1926-1948
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Labor Education Service (ALES)
5225 L
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents), plays (performed works).
8209473
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
A. Holland-Loucks, August 02, 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 21, 2017
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5225: ALES Records 5225 C: ALES Course Materials 5225 E: ALES Labor Education Records 5225 I: ALES International Labor Records 5225 S: ALES Scrapbooks 5225 MB: ALES Pearl L. Willen Memorial Memorabilia
American Labor Education Service
8209473
- "A" Files, 1935-1943 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- "A" Files Folder #2, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- "B" Files, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- "B" Files Folder #2, 1933-1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- "C" Files, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- "D" Files, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- "E" Files, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- "F" Files, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- "F" Files Folder #2, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- "G" Files, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- "H" Files, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- "I" Files (Box 1, Folder 12)
- "J" Files (Box 1, Folder 13)
- "K" Files (Box 1, Folder 14)
- "L" Files, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- "L" Files Folder #2 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- "M" Files, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- "M" Files Folder #2, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- "N" Files, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- "O" Files, 1929-1938 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- "O" Files Folder #2, 1927-1943 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- "P" Files, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- "R" Files, 1932-1941 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- "S" Files, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- "S" Files Folder #2, 1938-1942 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- "S" Files Folder #3, 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- "S" Files Folder #4, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- "T" Files, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- "U" Files, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- "V" Files, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- "W" Files, 1932-1938 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- "W" Files Folder #2, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- "W" Files Folder #3, 1929-1939 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Untitled, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- New Theatre League, 1938-1942 (Box 2, Folder 13)